in this lesson we will explore some of
在本课中 我们将探讨一些
the tools in the toolbox I'll
工具箱里的工具我会
demonstrate on a blank 8x10 canvas we
在空白的8x10画布上演示我们
already know what the brush tool can do
我已经知道画笔工具可以做什么
so we'll skip that one beside the brush
所以我们跳过笔刷旁边的那个
tool are the shape tools these have a
工具是形状工具 这些工具具有
dual purpose first they can be used to
两用首先 它们可以用来
draw straight lines curves and geometric
绘制直线、曲线和几何图形
shapes with the brush tool and second
使用画笔工具和第二个
they can be used to draw Vector shapes
它们可用于绘制矢量形状
Vector art is its own in-depth subject
向量艺术是它自己的深度学科
and we'll be focusing more on creating
我们将更专注于创造
roster art in this course so I will only
这门课的花名册艺术 所以我只会
give an overview of what you can do with
概述一下你可以做些什么
the vector tools and Creed it I have a
矢量工具和信条我有一个
reference video you can watch if you
您可以在以下情况下观看参考视频
want to learn more about creating Vector
想了解有关创建向量的更多信息
art the line tool will enable you to
艺术线工具将使您能够
draw straight lines with whatever brush
用任何画笔画直线
is currently selected tap and drag to
当前处于选中状态 点击并拖动到
create the start and end points hold
创建起点和终点保持
still and you'll see a preview of the
仍然 您将看到预览
line release to draw the line holding
线条松开 拉线按住
shift will constrain the lines to 15°
Shift将线条限制为15°
angles you can also draw a line but
角度你也可以画一条线 但是
before releasing hold all to drag the
在松开全部按住键以拖动
line to a new
线路转到新的
location another way to access the
位置另一种访问
straight line mode is to select the
直线模式是选择
brush tool then hold V here's a pro tip
画笔工具 然后按住V 这是一个专业提示
if you're using Windows 10 or 11 you can
如果您使用的是Windows 10或Windows 11 您可以
download and install Microsoft power
下载并安装Microsoft POWER
toys which is a free application that
玩具 这是一个免费的应用程序
can add some Art and Design related
我可以添加一些与艺术和设计相关的内容
functions to your computer the feature I
功能对您的计算机起作用
want to focus on is the crosshairs under
想要重点关注的是下面的十字准线
Mouse utilities these are independent of
这些鼠标实用程序独立于
the crosshairs you get inside Creed
你在Creed里面得到的十字准线
these work in any application and can be
它们可以在任何应用程序中工作 并且可以
enabled and disabled with a keyboard
使用键盘启用和禁用
shortcut mine is set to contrl alt shift
捷径矿将控制换挡
X I have a reference video you can watch
我有一段参考视频 你可以看
if you want to learn more as you can see
如果您想了解更多信息 如您所见
by enabling these I can use the
通过启用这些功能 我可以使用
crosshairs to align the points of my
用十字准线对齐我的
lines more easily now I can avoid
现在我可以更容易地避免排队了
overdrawing the line when I am done with
当我用完的时候透支这条线
them I can hide the windows crosshairs
他们 我可以隐藏窗户的十字准线
with the same shortcut I have this
用同样的捷径我有这个
shortcut programm to a button on my
指向我的按钮的快捷程序
stream deck but you can also set it to
Stream Deck 但您也可以将其设置为
an Express key the straight line mode
快捷键进入直线模式
also works with other brush tools
也可与其他画笔工具配合使用
including the erasers and blenders I'll
包括橡皮和搅拌机 我会
explain how it works with Vector layers
解释它如何使用矢量层
later each tool has a set of properties
之后 每个工具都有一组属性
you can access from the tool options
您可以从工具选项访问
panel I have mine docked on the left for
面板我已将我的停靠在左侧
the straight line brush I can choose to
我可以选择的直线画笔
show or hide the line preview among
在其中显示或隐藏线预览
other settings most of the time if
在大多数情况下进行其他设置
you're using a tool you'll want to have
您正在使用的工具是您想要拥有的
this panel open as well in addition to
此面板也会打开
drawing straight lines you can also draw
画直线你也可以画
rectangles and ellipses you can even
长方形和椭圆形你甚至可以
choose to fill these shapes with a color
选择用颜色填充这些形状
by choosing foreground color the fill
通过选择前景色填充
and stroke will be the same color
和笔触将是相同的颜色
background color is the Swatch here in
背景颜色是此处的色板
the color selector you can use this to
您可以使用该颜色选择器来
choose a different color from the stroke
选择与笔触不同的颜色
you can juxtapose these colors as well
你也可以把这些颜色并列在一起
you can also draw free form polygonal
您还可以绘制自由形式的多边形
shapes using the polygon and polyline
使用多边形和多段线的形状
tools the polygon tool creates closed
面工具创建闭合的工具
shapes while the poly line tool creates
形状 同时折线工具创建
open shapes holding shift and clicking
按住Shift键并单击以打开形状
will close the shape or end the line
将关闭形状或结束线条
the beer curve tool works well for
啤酒曲线工具适用于
drawing curved lines but you'd be better
画曲线 但你会做得更好
off using a vector layer for this since
关闭使用矢量层 因为
you'd be able to edit the curves after
在此之后 您将能够编辑曲线
drawing them if you try this tool you'll
绘制它们如果您尝试此工具 您将
see that it can be cumbersome to work
确保工作起来会很繁琐
with you have to drag out the curves at
你必须拖出曲线的位置
each point if you'd like to draw these
每一点 如果你想画这些
shapes freehand with a bit of assistance
在一点帮助下形成徒手造型
to make the line smoother straight you
为了让你的线条更顺畅
can use the freehand path tool right now
现在可以使用手绘路径工具
it's set to curve so I can draw curved
它被设置为曲线 这样我就可以画曲线了
lines that get smoothed out if I set it
如果我设置了它 线条就会变得平滑
is straight then I get lines that are
是直的 然后我得到的台词是
automatically straightened you can set
自动拉直即可设置
the tolerance of this smoothing as well
这种平滑的容忍度也是如此
using the optimize value for a bit more
使用优化值可获得更多信息
control over line smoothing you can use
控制您可以使用的线条平滑
the dynamic brush tool this has mass and
该动态画笔工具具有质量和
drag properties that concretely slow
拖动具体减慢速度的属性
down your brush making it easier to draw
放下你的画笔 让它更容易画出来
accurately smoothing or brush
精确平滑或画笔
stabilization can be applied to the
稳定化可以应用于
regular freehand brush tools as well
也有普通的写意画笔工具
basic smoothing adds a small amount of
基本平滑添加了少量的
smoothing to reduce wobble in your lines
流畅处理以减少线条的抖动
without slowing them down too much this
而不会让他们慢太多
is necessary if you're using an older
如果您使用的是较旧的
drawing tablet or a cheap brand that
图画平板电脑或廉价品牌
doesn't have very good pen technology if
如果没有很好的笔技术
you're not having any stability issues
你不会有任何稳定性问题
then you can leave smoothing disabled if
然后 如果出现以下情况 则可以禁用平滑
you want a higher amount of smoothing
您希望获得更高的平滑度
then choose a weighted or stabilizer
然后选择加权或稳定器
higher values will stabilize your stroke
较高的值将稳定您的中风
more in particular the stabilizer mode
更特别的是稳定器模式
really keeps your line from wobbling
真的能让你的线条不会摇晃
even if you have a very shaky hand or
即使你的手很颤抖 或者
you're using a mouse to draw you can
您正在使用鼠标来绘制您可以
fine-tune these settings to get the
微调这些设置以获得
exact degree of stabilization you need
您需要的确切稳定程度
the downside to all this Precision is
所有这些精确度的缺点是
that a stable brush makes it very
一把稳定的刷子使它非常
difficult to draw fast and Loosely so
很难画得又快又松
unless you need a very stable line for
除非你需要一条非常稳定的生产线
inking or something of that nature leave
墨水之类的东西留下了
this setting very low or even disabled
此设置非常低 甚至被禁用
since you cannot save smoothing settings
因为您不能保存平滑设置
per brush it can be inconvenient to have
对于每个刷子 可能不太方便
to keep turning it on and off what might
不断地打开和关闭它可能
be easier is to make a custom keyboard
更简单的是制作一个定制的键盘
shortcut to enable and disable it and
启用和禁用它的快捷方式
maybe even program that to an Express
也许甚至可以将其编程为Express
key the final tool in this row is the
关键字该行中的最后一个工具是
multibrush tool this allows you to paint
多画笔工具此工具允许您绘制
with symmetry as you can see my line is
你可以看到我的线条是对称的
mirrored and I can create a nice mandala
镜面和我可以创造一个很好的曼陀罗
effect I can edit the number of symmetry
效果我可以编辑对称的个数
planes known as brushes and even use
被称为刷子的平面 甚至使用
different modes to get various
不同的模式可以获得不同的
effects the next row down contains the
效果下一行包含
move and transformation tools to really
移动和转变工具以真正实现
explore what these can do we need to
了解这些功能的功能 我们需要
have something on a couple of different
有几个不同的东西
layers
层层
you can click on the plus button in the
你可以点击加号按钮
layers panel to create a new default
用于创建新的默认设置的图层面板
layer and draw something on both layers
分层并在两个层上绘制一些内容
or you can use my transform tool
或者 您可以使用我的变换工具
template to follow along with me let's
跟我一起走的模板让我们
start with the move tool you might get
从移动工具开始 您可能会看到
this confused with the arrow shaped tool
这与箭头形状的工具混淆了
near the top called the select shapes
靠近顶部的部分称为选择形状
tool but if you try to use that CR will
工具 但如果您尝试使用该CR将
let you know it's intended for Vector
让你知道这是为向量准备的
shapes whichever layer is currently
形状 无论当前是哪一层
selected will be moved by the move tool
所选内容将通过移动工具进行移动
I'll select the red ball layer and I can
我将选择红色球层 然后我可以
drag that layer around the canvas
在画布周围拖动该层
I can even select multiple layers by
我甚至可以通过以下方式选择多个层
holding shift or control and move them
按住Shift或Ctrl并移动它们
together I can also constrain the
同时 我还可以约束
movement of a layer to a horizontal or
将层移动到水平或
vertical axis by holding shift a quick
按住Shift键快速设置垂直轴
way to select this tool is to press t to
选择此工具的方法是按t键
the left in the toolbx is the transform
Toolbx中的左侧是转换
tool this tool allows you to move
工具此工具允许您移动
objects around the canvas as well but it
画布周围的对象也一样 但它
can also enlarge reduce rotate and
还可以放大、缩小、旋转和
distort layers but we'll come back to
扭曲层 但我们将回到
that in a later lesson I'll select the
在后面的课程中 我将选择
black ball layer and move then enlarge
黑色球层并移动 然后放大
it by dragging the outer edges of the
通过拖动
box or the corners when I am finished I
包厢还是角落当我做完的时候
can end the transformation in a couple
可以在一段时间内结束转换
of ways first I can select a different
首先我可以选择不同的方式
tool like one of the brushes and second
工具 比如其中一把刷子和第二把
I can press enter on my keyboard
我可以按键盘上的Enter键
pressing escape will reset the
按Ess键将重置
transformation while keeping it active
在保持活跃的同时实现转型
sort of like an undo you can also press
有点像撤消 您也可以按
contrl T to activate the transform
Ctrl T以激活变换
tool multiple layers can be transformed
工具可变换多个层
as
AS
well now that we know how to move layers
现在我们知道了如何移动层
around and transform them we can go back
绕过他们 改变他们 我们可以回到过去
to the shape tools and briefly examine
添加到形状工具 并简要查看
how they can be used to draw in Vector
如何使用它们在矢量中绘制
I'll return to the blank 8x10 canvas
我将返回到空白的8x10画布
you'll need to click the arrow next to
您需要单击旁边的箭头
the plus button in the layers panel to
层面板中的加号按钮可用于
create a new vector layer to let cre
创建一个新的矢量层以使cre
know that you want to use these tools
知道您想要使用这些工具
for Vector
对于向量
illustration now if I use any of the
现在说明如果我使用任何
shape tools I will get a vector line
形状工具我会得到一条矢量线
instead of a brush stroke I can use the
而不是画笔笔触 我可以使用
select shapes tool to move the shapes
选择形状工具以移动形状
and transform them like I can with a
就像我可以用一个
default layer the advantage is that I
默认层的优点是我
can also use the edit shape tool to
也可以使用编辑形状工具执行以下操作
freely edit the shape of these lines for
自由编辑这些线条的形状
example I can round the edges of this
例如 我可以绕过这一段的边缘
Square by dragging the corner and in the
通过拖动角和在
tool options if I choose convert to path
选择转换为路径时的工具选项
I'll get nodes that I can use to reshape
我将获得可用于重塑的节点
this more precisely you can also easily
这更准确地说 你也可以很容易地
edit the stroke and fill colors of
编辑的笔触和填充颜色
vector shapes in the tool options panel
工具选项面板中的矢量图形
you can even fill shapes with gradients
您甚至可以使用渐变填充形状
if I reshape the vector layer The Fill
如果我重塑向量层的填充
adjusts automatically but perhaps the
自动调整 但可能是
greatest Advantage is that Vector art is
最大的优势是向量艺术是
resolution indep dependent so it can be
分辨率依赖于索引 因此它可以
enlarged without losing visual quality
在不损失视觉质量的情况下放大
to remove Vector shapes select them with
要删除矢量形状 请使用选择它们
the select shapes tool and then press
选择形状工具 然后按
delete or delete the entire layer again
再次删除或删除整个层
to keep this course concise I won't say
为了保持这一过程的简明扼要 我不会说
much more about Vector art let's explore
关于向量艺术的更多信息 让我们来探索
the text tool next text is another type
文本工具下一个文本是另一种类型
of vector shape you can create in Crea
可以在Crea中创建的矢量形状的
though you can add it to default layers
虽然您可以将其添加到默认图层
it's better to do it in Vector so you
最好是在向量中进行 这样你就可以
don't lose visual quality when scaling
缩放时不会损失视觉质量
the font up and down drag a box where
字体向上和向下拖动一个方框到
you'd like to place the text the edit
您想要将文本放入编辑
text panel appears and you can use it to
文本面板出现 您可以使用它来
enter your desired text and choose its
输入所需文本并选择其
properties like font size and color you
字体大小和颜色等属性
can resize this panel to make it smaller
可以调整此面板的大小以使其更小
but unfortunately you have to close it
但不幸的是你不得不把它关了
to do anything with a text layer this is
要对文本层执行任何操作 请执行以下操作
very inconvenient so I would recommend
非常不方便 所以我建议
using a different application for your
使用不同的应用程序
text if you use it a lot you can always
如果你经常使用它 你总是可以
make the artwork in cre and then the
在cre中制作图稿 然后
text and something else using a cross-
文本和其他使用叉号的内容-
compatible file format like
兼容的文件格式 如
PSD next we will go back down to the the
PSD接下来我们将回到下面的
crop tool which can crop or enlarge the
可裁剪或放大的裁剪工具
canvas I'll load the canvas size
画布我将加载画布大小
template to work with the crop tool is
使用裁剪工具的模板为
most commonly used to make the canvas
最常用于制作画布
smaller by trimming off excess space so
通过削减多余的空间而变得更小
if I want to trim this canvas down I'll
如果我想把这块画布剪下来 我会
drag a box where I want to remove the
将一个框拖到要删除的位置
canvas when you're cropping by eye
当你用眼睛裁剪时的画布
you're creating an arbitrary crop if
如果您创建的是任意裁剪 则
you're just posting your artwork to the
你只是把你的作品发布到
web the crop dimensions are not so
Web上的裁剪维度并非如此
important but if you'll be printing your
重要 但如果您要打印您的
work I'd recommend cropping to a
我建议把工作剪成
specific print size you can set a
您可以设置特定的打印大小
specific crop size in the tool options
工具选项中的特定裁剪大小
you can also lock and edit the aspect
您还可以锁定和编辑特征
ratio for example a setting of one will
比方说 设置为1将
make the crop perfectly Square I'm going
把剪裁做得完美正方形我要去
to press enter to commit that crop and
按Enter键提交该裁剪 然后
now that outside area has been trimmed
现在外面的区域已经被修剪掉了
away this part of the painting will be
把这幅画的这一部分去掉
permanently removed if I save my artwork
如果保存我的图稿 则永久删除
if I want the cropped area to return I
如果我想让裁剪过的区域归还我
can undo to the point before I had
可以撤销到我之前的那一点
applied the
应用了
crop I'll switch to a blank 8x10 canvas
裁剪我将切换到空白的8x10画布
and next is the gradient tool which
接下来是渐变工具 它
allows you to create a gradient by
允许您通过以下方式创建渐变
dragging it across the canvas the
在画布上拖动它
gradient will flow between the start and
坡度将在起点和
end points you can also choose gradient
终点也可以选择渐变
presets from the properties bar there is
属性栏中的预设有
a foreground color to transparent
要透明的前景色
gradient as well as many other color
渐变以及许多其他颜色
combinations you can even change the
组合 您甚至可以更改
gradient shape from linear to radial and
从线性到径向的渐变形状和
many other
许多其他人
modes the sample tool we already
对我们已经创建的示例工具进行建模
explored in an earlier lesson we can use
在前面的课程中探索过 我们可以使用
this to sample colors from the canvas
这将从画布中采样颜色
there's more that this tool can do but
这个工具还可以做更多的事情 但是
we'll get into into that in a dedicated
我们将在一个专门的
lesson next is the paint bucket tool the
下一课是油漆桶工具
paint bucket tool can flood fill areas
油漆桶工具可以泛洪填充区域
of your canvas let's open the paint
在你的画布上让我们打开油漆
bucket tool template for this the crop
用于此裁剪的铲斗工具模板
tool is most commonly used to make the
工具最常用于制作
canvas smaller by trimming off excess
通过修剪多余的画布使画布变小
space hard Edge brush this tool has a
空间硬边笔刷此工具有一个
lot of properties so let's expand the
有很多属性 所以让我们扩展
panel to show them all I'll also reset
显示它们的面板 我还将重置
the settings so they are all at their
这些设置使它们都处于各自的状态
defaults basically the Paint Bucket
基本上是默认的油漆桶
detects differences in color and uses
检测颜色和用途的差异
those differences to limit the color
这些差异限制了颜色
fill to a specific boundary with these
用这些填充到特定边界
settings here I can select the circle
此处设置我可以选择圆圈
lines layer and fill those shapes you
线条分层并填充这些形状
may notice that when you try to fill the
您可能会注意到 当您尝试填充
top right Circle the paint floods
右上角圆圈油漆泛滥
outside of the shape that's because that
形状之外 那是因为
circle is not closed like the other
圆圈不像其他圆圈一样是封闭的
shapes so the paint has a way to escape
形状 这样油漆就有了逃逸的途径
its boundary I'll undo those fills by
它的边界 我会撤销这些填充
reverting my template you can do this by
要恢复我的模板 您可以执行以下操作
simply reopening the file one key
只需重新打开文件One Key
feature to be aware of is the reference
需要注意的功能是参考
setting the second option will allow the
设置第二个选项将允许
paint Buton to detect differences in
绘制按钮以检测其中的差异
color on all layers so if I select the
所有层上的颜色 因此如果我选择
color fill layer and fill there The Fill
给填充层上色 并在那里填充
is separate from the line work by
通过以下方式与线路工作分开
growing the edge of the fill by two
将填方边缘增加两倍
pixels I can even get it to fill Beyond
像素我甚至可以让它填充到更远的地方
the Edge of the line art this makes for
这就是线条艺术的边缘
a clean more professional coloring job
一份干净、更专业的涂色工作
the drag fill mode will even allow you
拖曳填充模式甚至可以让你
to drag across cells to fill them in
在单元格之间拖动以填充单元格的步骤
this can greatly speed up your coloring
这可以大大加快你的上色速度
workflow the enclos and fill tool is
封闭和填充工具的工作流程为
another more advanced aned way to fill
另一种更高级的填充方式
line art I'll reset the settings and
艺术线条我将重置设置并
revert the template you can choose from
还原可供选择的模板
a variety of ways to make a selection
选择的方式多种多样
including shapes a lasso or a brush I'll
包括形状 套索或刷子 我会
choose the lasso next you can Define
选择下一个可以定义的套索
exactly what should be filled in in this
到底应该在这里面填什么
case I'll set the target regions to any
如果我将目标区域设置为任何
surrounded by a specific color and
周围环绕着一种特定的颜色
choose black since that's what we want
选择黑色 因为这是我们想要的
to use as the fill boundary I'll also
要用作填充边界 我还将
grow The Fill by two pixels set the
将填充放大两个像素设置为
reference to all layers and fill onto
引用所有层并填充到
the fill layer now if I draw a selection
如果我绘制选区 现在填充层
around the star shape you can see it's
在星形周围 你可以看到它是
filled in perfectly but the real
填写得很完美 但却是真实的
advantage of this tool is that I can
这个工具的优点是我可以
undo and then draw a selection around
撤消 然后在周围绘制选区
the star and the circle to fill
星星和圆圈要填满
everything at once this is very
一切同时发生这非常
time-saving if you have a lot of small
如果你有很多小的 节省时间
cells to fill in if you prefer you can
如果您愿意 可以填写单元格
also use the brush mode to paint over
也可以使用画笔模式来绘制
what you want to fill there is a lot
你想填的东西很多
more you can do to fine-tune this tool
您可以做更多事情来微调此工具
but it's too much to cover in this
但这太多了 无法涵盖
course the techniques for coloring line
课程上色技术
artart are something I cover in a
艺术是我在
reference video so I will refer you to
参考视频 所以我会向您推荐
that if you would like to learn more I
如果您想了解更多信息
also have a reference video that covers
还有一个参考视频 涵盖
coloring specifically with the colorized
专门用有色人种上色
mask tool in cre so I won't repeat that
cre中的面具工具 所以我不会重复
information here that concludes our
此处的信息结束了我们的
exploration of the toolbox there are a
工具箱的探索有一个
few other tools we skipped over like the
我们跳过的其他一些工具 例如
selection Tools assistant and reference
选择工具助理和参考
image tools we will come back to these
我们将回到这些图像工具
in a later lesson tools such as the
在稍后的课程中 工具 例如
measure smart patch and calligraphy I
测量智能补丁和书法I
don't find to be essential coming up
不觉得接下来是必要的
next we will be exploring the menu bar
接下来我们将探索菜单栏
commands like file edit
文件编辑等命令
Etc
等